Antonio Guzmán Vilchis

Frontend Developer

aguzmanv09@gmail.com <u>agvcoder.com</u> CDMX, México +52 55-18-26-22-52

Profile

I am a Frontend developer with javascript and typescript, I am passionate about the world of web development, my main focus is to create high impact applications in society, my goals as a web developer is to specialize within the frontend area in a company that fits my values. I am also studying a degree in computer engineering within the metropolitan autonomous university (UAM-C)

Academic

Computer Engeneering UAM-C

To train critical, creative professionals with social responsibility and ethical commitment, trained in advanced technologies.

Actual

Javascript/React Platzi

Know the Javascript language, developing basic routines and programs using the language and Developing static websites using HTML and CSS

Jul 2020

Experience

Eduli Lead Frontend

School administration platform, using React and sass technologies.

Apr 2020 - Current

CREA Lead Frontend

Create tools to impact communities of entrepreneurs

Feb 2021 - Current

SitDigital Frontend

Work with technologies such as React, cells, Polymer 2 and HTML/CSS as a team to create frontend solutions for different types of clients.

Feb 2021 - Sep 2021

Freelance Fullstack

Develop different types of web solutions (Landing, E-commerce, Apps) mainly with the Javascript/Typescript language and technologies such as React, NodeJs.

Jul 2020 - Feb 2021

Skills

Javascript

Typescript

React

HTML/CSS

SASS

Node

Interest

Education Frontend UI & UX React

Startup New challenges

Languages

Spanish

English



